Renato de Oliveira Picco – Brazilian 37 years old

Street: Av Presidente João Goulart, 6 - zip code: 06036-048 Complement: Tower Copacabana Apartament 43 - Umuarama

City/State: Osasco/São Paulo

Mobile: +55 (11) 98494 4825 | e-mail: repicco@hotmail.com

Professional Focus

Frontend web developer - ReactJS

Review

+15 years of experience at TI, making new technologies for clients, support, planning and running projects.

6 years with focus at developer Frontend, making system, websites and banners with: Jquery, JavaScript, ReactJS and VueJS(2 and 3).

Using Design Patterns like MVC and DDD. Main focus when use DDD in tests with Jest and Cypress.

Skills:

Intermediary:

Javascript + ES6, React.Js / React Native, Nextjs, VueJs 2 e 3 (Vuex), HTML5, CSS3, SPA, PWA, Flexbox, Styled Components, Bootstrap, Materialize, SASS, AXIOS, AJAX, APIs Rest (Json), Graphql, Websocket, Datatable and AmCharts.

Basic:

Angular, Jquery, Node.Js, PHP, Wordpress, SQL, MongoDB e Firebase...

Extras

Projects Methodology: Ágil – Scrum – Kanban

Version of codes with Git.

Formation

Course: Gestão de Ambientes de Internet e Redes Computacionais

Institution: Universidade Nove de Julho / São Paulo

English

Tech – <u>Advanced</u>
Calls and conversation - Intermediary
Read and Write – Intermediary

Course: English Studies Institution: Wise Up

Extra course:

Course: Manager ReactJs, React Native, Nodejs, Styled Components, Axios, Redux,

NextJs and Expo

Institution: Sujeito Programador - Progress

Course: Create Applications with Quasar (Vueis) and Firebase

Institution: Udemy (EAD) – Finish 27/03/2021.

Course: Vue Js - zero to advanced

Institution: Udemy (EAD) - Finish 08/02/2021.

Course: Dev. Frontend Full

Institution: Gama Academy – Finish 08/04/2020.

Course: Developer Web – HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap, PHP and SQL.

Institution: Udemy (EAD) - Finish 25/10/2019

Course: HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript

Institution: Udemy (EAD) - Finish 05/09/2019

Course: Web Responsive with HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript

Institution: Udemy (EAD) – Finish 01/06/2018

Course: HTML5 e CSS3 - Web Responsive Advanced **Institution:** TreinaWeb (EAD) – Finish 26/04/2018

History

2024 - Current job | Global Hitss | Dev Front-end Senior React

Manage the last software of React Js, and in another front use React Native to create new Features and support the last features. Using Redux + Saga to manage the states, create new components with the Architecture DDD and slice business, logic and presentation in different layers.

2022 - 2024 | Ultracon Consultoria | Dev Front-end Senior React JS

Create a new system, using React Js with Webpack to make a webcomponent for use in other Apps with Vue and BackboneJs.

Work with Graphql and Rest APIs for connection at backend, create new components and use MVC Architecture with SOLID Architecture, after migrating to another Architecture using DDD (Domain Driven Design).

2021 - 2022 | A55 Crédito | Dev Front-end Senior Vue JS

Settings at system for credentials, using Vuejs Framework, create modals, forms and connections to backend with Rest API. Support responsive website, working at SCRUM with other developers at the same local, using GIt and Pair Programming.

2020 - 2021 Newpost | Dev Front-end Pleno JS

Create websites, configurations and support for new projects to 6 apps, developer Dashboards with Datatable, AMCharts and resolve APIs with Backend.

Support Design team to make new Layouts and responsive web pages.

2020 | Oliver Latam | Dev Front-end Jr.

Configuration of Email-Marketing with HTML + CSS and animations with Google Web Designer.

2017 - Current job| Freelancer Front-end

Create websites SPA and PWA, with HTML, CSS, JS and ReactJS.

2006 – 2020 | Work with network and infrastructure projects